你得试试这块起司蛋糕
You have got to try this cheesecake.
我不是那么喜欢吃甜食…
You know, I'm not that much of a sweet tooth...
我的天啊，它好香浓
Oh, my God, it's so creamy!
那是我吃过最棒的起司蛋糕!
That's the best cheesecake I've ever had!
你在哪里买到它?
Where did you get this?
我回家时它就已经放在门口了 有人把它寄给我们
It was at the front door when I got home. Somebody sent it to us.
收件人不是你
This isn't addressed to you.
收件人是楼下的布雷曼太太!
This is addressed to Mrs. Braverman downstairs!
小偷!
Thief!
我没看收件人姓名就打开了盒子…
I didn't read the box before I opened it...
盒子已经打开了就无法退还!
...and you can't return a box after you opened it!
-为什么? -因为它太好吃了
- Why not? - Because it's too delicious!
你偷了这个起司蛋糕，那是不对的
You stole this cheesecake. That's wrong.
不，没关系的 因为布雷曼太太会免费再收到一个
No, it'll be okay because Mrs. Braverman will send for a free one.
那可是双赢的局面
That way, we all win.
唯一的输家是大型起司蛋糕集团…
The only losers are the big cheesecake conglomerate...
“妈妈的小面包店”
..."Mama's Little Bakery."
我觉得好难过
I feel terrible.
我是个大坏蛋
I'm a horrible, horrible person.
对不起，你说什么?
I'm sorry, what?
Friends S07E11 起司蛋糕
The One With All The Cheesecakes
我得走了，我今天工作很忙
I should get going. Big day at work.
你们知道我怎么会昏迷不醒吗?
You know how I'm in a coma?
今天他们要帮我做检查 结果发现我没有脑死
Today they do a test on me and it turns out I'm not brain-dead.
所以…
So...
自作聪明先生
Mr. Smarty Pants.
没有脑死的是我演的角色
It's just my character that's not brain-dead.
菲比，今晚的事没取消吧?
Pheebs, still on for tonight?
-当然 -八点见
- Absolutely. - I'll see you at 8.
什么东西八点见?
What's at 8?
我们约好吃晚餐，我们大约每月会约一次去讨论你们的事
- Dinner. We get together about once a month to discuss the rest of you.
哇，我真的不知道
Wow! Did not know that.
我能说你今天看起来很漂亮吗?
May I say how lovely you look today?
那当然
Duly noted.
明天你要租辆车一起开过去吗?
So for tomorrow, do you want to rent a car and drive down together?
-你在说什么? -芬妮表妹的婚礼
- What are you talking about? - Cousin Frannie's wedding.
你被邀请了?
You were invited?
不
No.
我的天啊，我不敢相信
Oh, my God, I can't believe this.
我以为他们只邀请了爸跟妈
I thought only Mom and Dad were invited.
七岁到九岁，芬妮跟我形影不离
From the ages of 7 to 9, Frannie and I were inseparable.
或许九岁后，芬妮交了新朋友
Maybe since the age of 9, Frannie's made some new friends.
你要交些新朋友吗?
Do you wanna make some new friends?
或许这只是个误会 我打电话去问雪若阿姨
It's probably just a mistake. Let me call Aunt Cheryl.
或许他们邀请你了 只是请贴寄丢了
Maybe you are invited and the invitation got lost in the mail.
你可以打电话告诉她，我们小时候…
You call her and tell her that when we were kids...
她的宝贝芬妮好几次想脱光我的衣服
...her precious Frannie tried to undress me several times.
要不是我阻止了她，她也结不了婚
If I hadrt stopped her, there wouldn't be a wedding to go to.
她也想脱我的衣服
She tried to undress me too.
我以前会帮葛兰表弟脱衣服
I used to undress my cousin Glenn.
乔瑟夫弗朗西斯崔比亚尼 你回家了吗?
Joseph Francis Tribbiani, are you home yet?
我想他还没有回家，怎么了?
I think he's still out. What's wrong?
我得告诉你，瑞秋凯伦格林
I'll tell you, Rachel Karen Greene.
我跟乔伊有约 他留了这张字条给我
I had plans with Joey, and he left me this note.
菲比，我没办法赴约 我有约会，待会再谈
"Pheebs, can't make it. Got a date. Talk to you later.
大爹地
Big Daddy."
-大爹地? -那是我们之间的昵称
- "Big Daddy"? - That's a nickname we were trying.
你们为什么不试试“弗朗西斯”?
Why didn't you guys try "Francis"?
弗朗西斯这名字比钱德酷 不是吗?
Francis is a cooler name than Chandler, isn't it?
你知道什么样的昵称不会跟别人重复吗? “罗斯原子超人”
You know what nickname never caught on? "The Ross-a-tron."
乔瑟夫弗朗西斯回来了!
Here's Joseph Francis!
等一下，你干嘛叫我中间的名字?
Wait, what are you middle-naming me for?
我留了字条给你
I left you a note.
那不是放我鸽子的好理由
That doesn't give you the right to ditch me!
如果你有机会上床 当然可以取消跟朋友的约会
You can cancel plans with friends if there's a possibility for sex.
他说的对，这是规则
He's right. That is the rule.
-真的? -是的，我听到的就是那些
- Really? - Well, that's what I hear.
我从来没机会实施规则
I've never gotten a chance to actually employ the rule.
无法接受这种事，我们约好后 我期待你会出现
I don't accept it. When we make plans, I expect you to show up.
我不是你泡到女友前打发时间的代替品
I'm not a way to kill time till you meet someone better.
男女朋友来来去去 但朋友是一辈子的
Boyfriends and girlfriends will come and go, but this is for life.
我真的很抱歉 我不知道这对你来说那么重要
I'm so sorry. I had no idea it would bother you this much.
喔，它的确很重要
Well, it does.
我可以弥补吗?
Well, can I make it up to you?
对不起
I'm sorry.
明天晚上一起吃饭吧？ 我会自己付钱
How about dinner tomorrow night? I'll pay for myself.
好吧，你说服了我
Okay, you wore me down.
既然你站在那边，拿罐啤酒给“罗斯原子超人”吧?
While you're over there, how about a beer for "The Ross-a-tron"?
“罗斯…”它又回来了?
"Ross..." Is that back?
又有起司蛋糕
The other cheesecake came.
他们又把它送到这里来
They delivered it here again.
把它送到楼下去，那有什么问题?
Just bring it downstairs. What's the problem?
我不知道该怎么说再见
I can't seem to say goodbye.
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious?
两天前我们吃掉一个蛋糕 你还想再吃?
We ate an entire cake two days ago and you want more?
噢，我已经忘记它的味道了
Well, I've forgotten what it tastes like.
它是起司蛋糕，它很好吃
It was cheesecake. It was fine.
它又香又浓，酥酥的饼干…
It had a buttery, crumbly, graham cracker crust...
还有非常浓郁…
...with a very rich...
但不油腻的奶油起司
...yet light cream cheese filling.
我的嘴巴全是口水
Wow, my whole mouth just filled with saliva.
你知道吗? 忘了它，我们只是饿了
Know what? Forget it. We're just hungry.
我们没有吃午餐，所以头昏脑胀
We haven't had lunch. We're just lightheaded.
我们去吃午餐，忘了那个起司蛋糕吧
So let's go have lunch and forget about the cheesecake.
我们得把它还回去，才不会被诱惑
We'll drop it off so we're not tempted.
-你要去哪里吃午餐? -芝加哥妈妈的小面包店
- Where do you want to eat? - Mama's Little Bakery, Chicago.
梅尔托尔梅死了（最著名爵士歌王）
Mel Torme died.
乔伊，那是一年前的报纸
Joey, that paper's like a year old.
那表示山姆古迪商店的大特卖结束了？（音乐CD连锁店）
Does that mean the Sam Goody's sale is over?
我终于收到雪若阿姨的回音…
So I finally heard back from Aunt Cheryl...
很明显地这不是误会
...and apparently it wasn't a mistake.
婚礼现场座位有限…
There's limited seating...
座位有限? 我是个微小的人!
Limited seating? I am just one tiny person!
对，但是她不知道
Yeah, but she doesn't know that.
我是说上次她看到你…
I mean, the last time she saw you...
你会把婚礼用的小椅子压垮
...you'd have turned one of those little wedding chairs into kindling.
“座位有限”那真是个烂借口
"Limited seating." That's such a lame excuse.
那不是她不邀请我的原因
That's not the reason she's not inviting me.
那有什么大不了的呢? 我没被邀请观礼，只能去吃喜酒
What's the big deal?I wasn't invited to the ceremony, just the reception.
如果这能让你觉得开心一点 琼安和我只会去亮个相…
If it makes you feel any better, Joan and I will just make an appearance...
我们会提早离开，以示抗议
...and then we'll leave early as a sign of protest.
-琼安? -对，她是我的女伴
- Joan? - Yeah, my date.
她是语言系的助教，又高又漂亮
Assistant professor in linguistics. Tall, very beautiful.
虽然有些人说，别挑太魁梧的女孩
And despite what some people say, not broad-backed.
等一下，你收到的喜贴是“请携伴参加”?
Wait a minute. You got "Ross Geller and Guest"?
我没有被邀请，你却可以“携伴参加”?
I wasn't invited, and you got "and Guest"?
对不起，我真的得解释罗斯的行为
Excuse me, I do have to interrupt on Ross' behalf.
我想规则也适用在这里
I think the rule applies here.
因为他有机会跟魁梧女人上床…
Since he has a chance to get on broad-back...
她没有那么魁梧
Not broad-back!
兄弟，我见过她．她真的很魁梧
Dude, I've seen her. She's like a billboard.
等一下，你得带我去
Wait a minute. You're bringing me.
我不能取消琼安的约会
I can't cancel on Joan.
-为什么? -你没有听到吗?
- Why not? - Did you not hear me?
她是语言系的助教
She's an assistant professor in the linguistics department.
她们很辣
They're wild.
-你到底为什么想去? -因为…
- Why do you want to come anyway? - Because...
她是我表妹
...she's my cousin.
我们是一起长大的
I mean, we grew up together.
我们是家人，你知道吗？ 对我来说那很重要
Family, you know? And all that's important to me.
好吧，我带你去
Okay, all right. I'll take you.
我去打电话给琼安
I'll go call Joan.
那真的是太棒了
Oh, that's nice.
家人应该要出席的
Family should be there.
这是她的婚礼 她一生中最快乐的日子
It's her wedding. Happiest day of her life.
我们等着瞧吧
We'll see.
谢谢你请我吃午餐
Well, thank you for lunch.
等一下，我以为你付了钱
Wait, I thought you paid.
很明显的 我们不必再掏钱买食物了
Apparently, we don't pay for food anymore.
-我没有看错吧? -它还在那里
- Do you see what I see?- It's still there.
布雷曼太太一定是出去了
Mrs. Braverman must be out.
她可能出城去了或许几个月后才会回来
She could be out of town. Maybe gone for months.
到时候蛋糕一定坏了 不能让她回来看到坏掉的起司蛋糕
By then, it may spoil. She can't come back to bad cheesecake.
-她可能会中毒死掉 -我不希望发生那种事
- It could kill her. - Don't want that.
我们是在保护她
We're protecting her.
-我们把它拿走，-但是快一点
- We'll take it. - But quick.
-为什么? -我听到她在里面走动的声音
- Why? - I hear her in there.
快走…
Go! Go! Go!
你认为婚礼上穿白色花边衣服不合适吗
Do you think it's inappropriate to wear a white, lacy dress to a wedding?
-是的 -太好了
- Yes. - Excellent.
天啊，是大卫
Oh, my God, that's David.
-谁? -那个科学家大卫
- Who? - David, the scientist guy.
我爱上的那个大卫
David that I was in love with.
他到俄罗斯去，伤了我的心，大卫
Who went to Russia and broke my heart, David.
我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
只要一直念某人的名字 那个人就会转过身来
Say their name enough, they turn around.
菲比
Phoebe.
大卫
David.
你在做什么? 你不是在俄罗斯吗?
What are you doing? Aren't you supposed to be in Russia?
我到城里来开会
I'm just in town for a conference.
天啊，你看起来美得出奇
God, you look phenomenal.
噢…
Well...
对
Yeah.
你看起来也很棒 你剪了头发吗?
You look great too. Did you get a haircut?
对，我大概剪了三十次
Yeah. Well, I got like 30 of them.
听着，我得跟你坦诚一件事
Look, I got a confession to make.
我希望能在这里遇到你
I was hoping to run into you here.
我不知道该不该打电话给你 我只会在城里待几天…
I didn't know if I should call. I was only in town a few days...
我不想打扰你的生活
...and I didn't want to intrude on your life.
我真的想见你…
I really wanted to see you...
但我不知道你要不要见我
...but I didn't know if you wanted to see me.
我当然想见你，我常常想到你
Of course I would want to see you. I think about you all the time.
真的吗? 因为我也常常想到你
Really? Because I think about you all the time.
明斯克有一座雕像让我常常想起你
There's a statue in Minsk that reminds me of you so much.
事实上那是列宁的雕像…
It's actually of Lenin...
但有些角度…
...but, you know, at certain angles...
总之，今晚你想跟我共进晚餐吗?
Anyway, do you want to have dinner tonight?
好
Yes.
哦，不!
Oh, no!
-什么? -我不能
- What? - I can't.
我不敢相信，我有约了 明天可以吗?
I can't believe I have plans. Can you do it tomorrow?
不，再过几小时我就得离开 我得乘夜航回去
No, I have to go in a few hours. I have to be on the redeye.
听着，下次你到明斯克…
Listen, next time you're in Minsk...
菲比，我能跟你谈一谈吗?
Phoebe? Can I talk to you for a second?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我跟乔伊有约
I have plans with Joey.
所以呢? 他会谅解的
So? He'll understand.
不，他不会的，那根本不是重点
No, he won't. And that's not even the point.
我教训他不该取消朋友之间的计划
I made a whole speech about how you do not cancel plans with friends.
现在只因为可能是我真爱的人…
And now just because, potentially, the love of my life...
明天就要回俄罗斯去…
...returns from Russia for one night...
我就应该改变我的想法?
...I should change my beliefs?
我应该改变我的想法!
I should change my beliefs!
不，如果失去了原则那么我什么都不会有
No. If I don't have my principles, I don't have anything.
你意志太坚定了
You're so strong.
或许我可以赶快跟乔伊吃完晚餐 然后九点跟大卫见面
Or I should rush through dinner with Joey and meet David at 9.
我的天啊，那真的是太棒了!
Oh, my God, that is so good!
我吃饱了 但我知道如果我现在停下来
I'm full. And yet I know if I stop eating this...
我会后梅
...l'll regret it.
嘿，你们在吃什么?
Hey, what have you got there?
噢，那是…
Oh, it's...
豆腐蛋糕，你要吃一点吗?
It's tofu cake. Want some?
今晚你要做什么?
What are you doing tonight?
兄弟
Dude. Dude.
对不起
Sorry.
我跟菲比有约
I got plans with Phoebe.
真的? 莫妮卡说她九点有约会
Really? Monica said she had a date at 9.
-什么? 今晚? -莫妮卡是那么说的
- What? Tonight? - That's what Monica said.
她教训了我一顿 却同时约了我和她的男伴
After that speech, she makes a date on the same night she has plans with me?
她想草草解决大爹地
She's trying to pull a fast one on Big Daddy.
-现在请你别介意…-兄弟，兄弟!
- Now, if you'll excuse me... - Dude, dude!
如果我现在脱下裤子 你会什么感觉?
If I took off my pants right now, how would you feel?
就像你表弟葛兰
Like your cousin Glenn.
好了，我们的位置应该是这一桌
Here, I think this is us.
座位有限，我的天啊
Limited seating, my ass.
我们来看看谁被邀请了
Let's see who made the cut.
嗨，我是莫妮卡盖勒
Hi. I'm Monica Geller.
-你们跟新人是什么关系？ -我是芬妮以前的同事
- How do you know the bride and groom? - I worked with Frannie.
以前的同事，以前
Used to work with her. Used to.
我是她的亲戚却没有被邀请
I'm a relative and I didn't get invited.
我是她的血亲，血
A blood relative. Blood.
别在陌生人面前提到“血”
Stop saying "blood" to strangers.
从7岁到9岁，我们就不可分离 我甚至没被邀!
From the ages of 7 to 9, we were inseparable, and I didn't even get invited!
那你为什么在这里?
Then why are you here?
-和我哥哥约会 -嘿，我有约会，知道吗
- I'm my brother's date. - Hey, I had a date, okay?
简・特德斯基，语言学者
Joan Tedeschi, the linguist.
你呢? 你和快乐的新人什么关系?
So how about you? How do you know the happy couple?
我们是他们的大学同学
We went to college with both of them.
现在是他们的邻居
Now we live next door.
好吧，你还够格
Okay, you're fine.
你会喜欢上简的，她非常随和
You know, you would've liked Joan, she's very pleasant.
看那边!她的背影就像那样 不是很魁梧，对吧?
There! There! Her back looks like that.That's not broad, is it?
乔伊，该点菜了
Come on, Joey, you've got to be ready to order by now.
我不喜欢这张桌子 也许我们又要换了
You know, I don't I like this table either. Maybe we should move again.
不．就留在这里．对不起 我们要点菜了
No, we're staying right here. Excuse me, we're ready to order.
我不在这里工作
I don't work here.
那你就不该走来走去嘛
Well, then you shouldn't be walking around.
-你们要点菜了吗? -是的
- Are you guys ready? - Yes.
我要绿色沙拉，特调酱汁和水
I'll have a green salad, house dressing and water's fine.
你呢? 先生
And for you, sir?
对，慢烤鲑鱼…
Yeah. This slow-roasted salmon...
那到底有多慢呢?
...how slow are we talking?
它已经烤好了
It's already been roasted.
那么我不要，麻烦你再告诉我一次今日特餐
Oh, then no. Maybe I should hear the specials again.
我们已经听了三次
We've heard the specials three times.
有烤肋排，青花鱼跟特制龙虾馄饨
There's prime rib, mahi-mahi and a very special lobster ravioli.
-事实上我们没有馄饨了 -那么一切就都要改变了
- Actually, we're out of the ravioli. - Well, that changes everything!
你知道吗? 菲比 之前你说的话是对的
You know what, Pheebs? You were right before.
朋友太重要了
Friends are so important.
对，我很聪明，我知道
Yeah, I'm very wise. I know.
你知道我想做什么吗?
Know what I really want?
-什么? -我想花时间跟你长谈
- What? - Is to have a long, long talk.
你知道吗? 告诉我多一点人生道理
You know? Get Joey out on the open road and really open him up.
-可以点菜了吗? -是的
- Any progress? - Yes.
我要点龙虾馄饨
I will have the lobster ravioli.
天啊，乔伊，这得花一辈子的时间
God, Joey, this is taking forever.
-干嘛这么急呢? -噢…
- What's the rush? - Well...
我有个约会
...I have an appointment.
它非常重要
And it's very important.
怎么说?
What is it?
噢…
Well...
一个约会
...it's a date.
约会? 不，你一定弄错了 因为你不能约会…
- A date? - No, you must be mistaken, because you wouldn't have a date...
同时又跟朋友吃饭
...on the same night you have plans with a friend.
别让我觉得内疚
Don't make me feel badly.
不，我就是要那么做
No, I'm gonna!
我跟那个女孩出去你让我觉得非常内疚
You made me feel really guilty about going out with that girl.
好像我做了什么可怕的事 现在你也那么做
Like I did something terrible. Now you're doing the same thing.
才怪，这完全不一样
It's not! It's totally different!
我跟大卫有约，你还记得科学家大卫吗
This is with David. Remember David, the scientist guy?
对我来说他非常特别
He's very special to me.
那晚我约的女孩也很特别 她也是个科学家
My girl the other night was special. She was a scientist too.
-是吗? -她高中毕业
- She was? - Well, she graduated high school.
随便啦，你知道吗?
Whatever. Know what?
他只会在这里待四小时 我得去见他
He's only here for four hours and I'm gonna go see him.
-好吧 -对
- Fine! - Yeah.
你还在这里做什么? 我说过了，龙虾馄饨
What are you still doing here? I told you, lobster ravioli!
我正要离开，我以为你不会来了
I was about to leave. I didn't think you were coming.
我绝不会错过这次约会
I wouldn't have missed this.
我很高兴你来了
Well, I'm very glad you're here.
你是个绅士
Oh, you're such a gentleman.
来吧，到我家去
Come on, we're going to my place.
你想一个人独吞起司蛋糕?
Are you eating the cheesecake without me?
只要你现在能吹出口哨 我就给你一百块
I will give you $ 100 to whistle right now.
-你怎么可以不管我一个人独吞？ -你会怎么做呢?
- How can you eat it without me? - What'll you do?
告诉莫妮卡或乔伊? 不 你得把一切告诉他们
Tell Monica or Joey? No, you'd have to tell them everything.
我们是甜点小偷，我们犯了法
We're dessert stealers. We're living outside the law.
我不能让你跟起司蛋糕独处
I don't trust you with this cake.
我先发现它的，我要把它拿回来
I got it first, and I'm taking it back!
-什么? 不 -是的
- What? Oh, no. - Oh, yes.
你以为我就能相信你吗?
You think I trust you with it?
不，我们平分它
No, we'll split it.
那不公平，你已经吃掉一点了
That's not fair. You had some.
我想莫妮卡一定想知道…
I think Monica would be very interested to know...
你说她做的起司蛋糕“又干又粗”
...that you called her cheesecake "dry and mealy."
我们要用什么来切蛋糕?
What do we use to split it?
好了，挑一块
All right, pick a half.
这块比较大
Well, this side looks bigger.
但这块饼干比较多
But there's more crust on this side.
或者我该量一下…
Maybe if I measure it...
快挑一块
Pick a piece!
-好吧，我挑那一块 -那一块比较小
- All right, I pick that one. - It's the smaller piece.
好了，拿去吧
Okay. There you go.
好好享受你的蛋糕吧 我的朋友，因为大势己定
Enjoy your half, my friend. But that is it.
我不会跟你分，或跟你换 别哭着跑来找我…
No sharing, no switching, and don't come crying to me...
如果一下子就把蛋糕吃完了
...if you eat your piece too fast.
-你要给我一点蛋糕吗? -不
- You gonna give me some of yours? - Oh, no.
我不会跟你分，或跟你换 别哭着跑来找我…
No switching, no sharing. And don't come crying to me.
我要坐在这里花一整天好好享用我的蛋糕
I may just sit here and have my cake all day.
我要坐在走廊上吃我的…
Just sit here in the hallway and eat my...
罗斯，甜心!
Ross, sweetheart!
嘿，米莉阿姨
Oh, hey, Aunt Millie.
-这个婚礼很温馨吧? -没错
- Isn't it a beautiful wedding? - Yes, it is.
她每次都亲嘴巴!
Every time, on the lips!
为什么? 为什么要亲嘴巴?
Why? Why on the lips?
芬妮在那边 她看到我一定会很高兴吧
There's Frannie. Wort she be happy to see me?
你得乖乖的，好吗?
You be nice, all right?
我不是带你来欺负她
I didn't bring you to ambush her.
芬妮把你的《花花公子》拿给妈妈看
Frannie was the one who showed your Playboys to Mom.
那个贱人
That bitch.
莫妮卡!
Monica!
为什么…?
What...?
我在这里做什么? 你看到我很讶异吗
Am I doing here? Surprised to see me?
罗斯带我来的，你还喜欢吗?
Ross brought me. How do you like that?
芬妮，恭喜
Hi, Frannie. Congratulations.
你邀请我的家人却不邀请我，为什么?
You invite my whole family, and not me? Why?
你为什么不希望我来? 我做了什么?
Why wouldn't you want me here? What could I have done?
斯图沃特!
Stuart!
我相信你认识我丈夫
I believe you know my husband.
问题应该是，你做了“谁”
So it's really a question of "who" could you have done.
我讨厌这样，但我得走了
I hate this, but I have to go.
我不能错过飞机
I can't miss my flight.
我想下一班飞往明斯克的飞机是在…
I bet there's another flight to Minsk in...
七月
July.
听起来好美，它是什么意思?
That's really beautiful. What does it mean?
“请帮我把烧杯洗干净”
"Please clean my beakers."
我不常离开实验室
I don't get out of the lab much.
我以为它有别的意思
I thought it meant something else.
对，事实上，我想说…
Yeah, well, I really actually wanted to say...
那个
...that.
我想或许我不该说，因为…
But I figured I probably shouldn't because...
我得离开
...I have to leave.
不，你说的对，别说
No, you're right. Don't say it.
但我真的那么想
I do, though.
我也是
I do too.
再见，菲比
Well, bye, Phoebe.
现在不是时候，乔伊 明天你可以骂我
Now's not the time, Joey. You can yell at me tomorrow.
等一下，不，菲比，我不会骂你
Wait, no, Pheebs. I'm not gonna yell at you.
我只是开始想到你跟大卫…
I just started thinking about you and David...
我记得他第一次离开时你有多难过
...and I remember how bummed you were the first time he left.
菲比，过来
Oh, Pheebs, come here.
-你还好吧? -不，我一点都不好
- Are you okay? - No, I'm not okay.
我唯一喜欢的男人要去明斯克…
The only guy I've ever been crazy about is going to Minsk...
或许我永远都不会再见到他
...and I may never see him again.
你可以去看他
You could always visit him.
对，你以为他们会给我护照
Right. Like they'll let me have a passport.
有什么我可以帮忙的吗? 什么都行
Anything I can do? Whatever you need.
喔…
Well, now...
如果你可以比他先蒸馏出副原子粒子
...if you achieve distillation of subatomic particles before he does...
他就可以回来了
...then he could come back.
我可以试试看
I could give it a shot.
你看! 有一小块没有沾到地板
Oh, look! There's a piece that doesn't have floor on it.
-别越界! -快点!
- Stick to your side! - Come on, now!
好了，我们要吃什么?
All right, what are we having?
-等一下，我忘了拿披肩。-好吧，我在这里等你
- Oh, wait, I forgot my wrap. - Oh, I'll wait here for you.
-我不能回去! -为什么?
- I can't go back there! - Why?
你看到斯图沃特盯着我吗？ 他可能还想要我
Did you see the way Stuart was staring at me? I think he still wants me.
-我的天哪 -进去帮我拿!
- Oh, my God. - Just go do it!
好吧，等着
All right, wait here.
嗨，甜心! 你要走了吗?
Hi, sweetie! Are you leaving?
-喔… -亲阿姨一下，快点
- Well... - Give us a kiss. Come on.
为什么? 为什么要亲嘴巴?
Why? Why on the lips?